

QUANG TRUONG

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

LINKEDIN GITHUB

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Finnish Novice
- Vietnamese Native

PROFILE

Quang is a Full Stack Developer with leadership qualities and lasting experience in managing teams across different industries. Earning a Bachelor's degree in Environmental Engineering in 2018 helped Quang to rekindle his passion for technology. Since then, Quang has remained determined about mastering full-stack development and putting his skills to action. Combining this passion with his experience in managing teams allows Quang to adapt to diverse environments and make a meaningful contribution.

RECENT PROJECTS

InstaFAKE

React.js, CSS, Firebase

A full-stack clone application built in order to demonstrate relevant skills.

Weather App

React.js, CSS

An application for fetching weather information from a public API based on the input location.

YouCube

React.js, CSS, YouTube API

A practice application built in order to strengthen the understanding of working with API in action.

SKILLS

Front-end Development: Accessibility, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, Redux, SCSS, TypeScript.

Back-end Development: Express.js, GraphQL, Node.js, REST API.

Database Management: Firebase, MongoDB.

Testing: Jest.

DevOps: GitHub Actions.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | October 2021 - Present

Shift Manager

K-Citymarket Jumbo | Vantaa, Finland | July 2020 - September 2021

- Oversaw the workflow and resolved issues occurring throughout 8-hour shifts.
- Managed other workers and ensured satisfaction at work.
- Responsible for ordering stock.
- Handled payments and communicated directly with customers.

Shift Manager

SSP Finland Oy | Helsinki, Finland | July 2019 - March 2020

- Oversaw the workflow and resolved issues occurring throughout 8-hour shifts.
- · Managed other workers and assisted them in daily operations.
- · Responsible for ordering stock.
- Took the role of a customer interface.

Shift Manager

Ai-To Foods Oy | Vantaa, Finland | October 2015 - July 2019

- Oversaw the operations in a warehouse and resolved issues occurring throughout shifts.
- · Responsible for ordering stock.
- · Managed other workers and ensured satisfaction at work.

EDUCATION

B.Eng. in Environmental Engineering

Metropolia University of Applied Sciences | Vantaa, Finland | October 2014 - May 2018